Sir, tell me how did you like ICICI LBR?
ICICI LBAR futures have a sell call
with a stop loss of 1920
for a target of 1865 1845 as operationally numbers have
come in weak.  Profit has also been slightly below expectations.
Management confidence seems to be slightly lower regarding pricing pressure.
It seems that pricing pressure will continue.
So I think and anyway
stocks are not moving with good results these days.
So you can fall a little on loose energy.  This has to be
seen.  Tata Alexa results are strong.   They are
looking quite good on every parameter.  There
is no problem.  Operational
performance is also quite good.  The stock
showed some interesting moves ahead of the results.
Ah in the last three months,
15% has also run in the last 1 month.  So let's see, a
good move has come.  So what
happens now?  If the numbers are good.  There will be
profit booking on the upside and if it comes down then one should
buy at the support level.  5700 and
5625 are two good supports for futures
and on the upside there is a
possibility of profit booking around 5885 5920.
Okay, with this all our guests are
included in the show.